stop.pk 2010-06-17

# PRIVACY POLICY - Largest Social Network of Pakistan by Pakistanis for Pakistanis

## The Information We Collect:

**This notice applies to all information collected on the Stop.pk Web site any time through any Service Pages.**

Personally Identifiable Information—When visiting Stop.pk and signing up for using Stop.pk services through any Service Page, you may choose to supply Stop.pk with information that identifies you personally. For End-Users, this information may include your name, email address, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, and other information.

Aggregate Information—We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services, and share the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties.

The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as email, search, community, advertising sales, ecommerce; completing an order; shipping a product; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy and the End-User Agreement, we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Clients and End-Users or to comply in responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal proceedings.

Finally, **we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.**

How You Can Access or Update Your Information

End-Users can access their information by logging in to their password-protected End-User account and selecting to update their "Personal Info."

If you have submitted information on our site but do not currently have an account with us, you can access and correct the information that we collect and maintain by contacting us and requesting such information or correction.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us by the contact us form located [here](http://stop.pk/contact-us/).

**Disclaimer**

Information on this website shall be deemed accurate and current only as of the date it is posted. Stop.pk specifically disclaims any duty to update.  
This website also contains third-party information and links to other Internet sites. Stop.pk takes no responsibility whatsoever for third-party information. Stop.pk specifically disclaims adoption or incorporation by reference of such information as its own. In addition to links to third party informational sites, Stop.pk has contracted with several external service providers. Though Stop.pk has contractural agreements to ensure confidentiality of information, Stop.pk assumes no responsibility for information that is voluntarily provided.

All images, graphs, text, or other content in this website are, to the extent permitted by law, copyrighted and otherwise proprietary. No reproduction, transmission or other use of this information is permitted without the prior written permission of Stop.pk.

Any unauthorized modification, tampering or change of any information, or any interference with the availability of or access to this website is strictly prohibited.

We reserve the right to modify the content of this website in any way, at any time, and for any reason without prior notification, and will not be liable in any way for possible consequences of such changes.

Stop.pk reserves all legal rights and remedies available.
